heartharena.com 2018-11-24

# Privacy Policy - Hearth Arena

This privacy policy sets out how HearthArena uses and protects any information that you give HearthArena when you use this website.

HearthArena may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from every now and then to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 25-05-2018.

## Data that we process

HearthArena processes your personal data by using our services and / or by providing this information to us. Below is an overview of the personal data we process:

  * a username and encrypted password that you create upon registration (or change later);
  * an e-mail address that you use during registration (or change later);
  * an IP address that you create or update your account with;
  * user submitted content that you actively provide for example statistics and data related to an arena deck you drafted using our website or drafting tools;
  * your internet browser and device type.

## Special and / or sensitive personal data that we process

Our website and / or service does not intend to collect data about website visitors who are younger than 16 years. Unless they have permission from parents or guardians. However, we cannot verify whether a visitor is older than 16. We encourage parents to be involved in the online activities of their children in order to prevent data about children being collected without parental consent. If you are convinced that we have collected personal information about a minor without this permission, please contact us at support [at] heartharena.com and we will delete this information.

## For what purpose and on what basis we process personal data

HearthArena processes your personal data for the following purposes:

  * to allow you to create an account;
  * to allow you to retrieve your account if you happen to lose your password;
  * to inform you about changes that are directly related to your account such as changes to this privacy policy or other service related notices;
  * to provide customer support
  * to investigate and help prevent security issues and abuse of our services;
  * to analyze your behavior and submitted data while using our website and tools to improve our products and services.

## Data Retention

HearthArena does not store your personal data longer than is strictly necessary to realize the goals for which your data is collected. At any point in time a user can request to terminate their account and all related data to it. You can find this feature in ‘my-account’ under ‘terminate account’.

## Sharing personal data with third parties

HearthArena will not sell your details to third parties and will only provide them if this is necessary for the execution of our agreement with you or to comply with a legal obligation. With companies that process your data in our assignment, we conclude a processor agreement to ensure the same level of security and confidentiality of your data. HearthArena remains responsible for these processing operations.

Upon account creation, a profile page is created with your arena statistics. Sensitive information like e-mail addresses or IPs are not shown on this page. We allow you to configure whether this profile link is accessible by other users. You can find this setting in ‘my account’ under ‘profile settings’.

Aggregated or anonymized data may be shared with partners or others for business or research purposes.

## Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

## Cookies, or similar techniques, that we use

HearthArena uses functional, analytical and tracking cookies. A cookie is a small text file that is stored in the browser of your computer, tablet or smartphone when you first visit this website. HearthArena uses cookies with a purely technical functionality. These ensure that the website works properly and that, for example, your preferred settings are remembered. These cookies are also used to make the website work well and to optimize it. In addition, we place cookies that keep track of your browsing habits so that we can offer customized content and advertisements. On your first visit to our website we have already informed you about these cookies and we have asked you for permission to place them. You can opt out of cookies by setting your internet browser so that it does not store cookies anymore. In addition, you can also delete all information previously saved via the settings of your browser. Sites like [cookiesandyou.com](https://cookiesandyou.com/) contains more information and instructions on how to this.

Cookies are also placed on this website by third parties. These are for example advertisers and / or social media companies. Below an overview:

Googly Analytics cookies:  
These cookies are used to measures website visits. We have entered a data processing agreement with Google and only anonymized IP addresses are used. You can opt-out for Google Analytics by using [Google's opt-out browser add-on](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/181881?hl=en).

Name: _ga  
Function: Google analytics uses this to distinguish users.  
Storage period: 2 years

Name: _gid  
Function: Google analytics uses this to distinguish users.  
Storage period: 24 hours

Name: _gat  
Function: Google analytics uses this to throttle request rate.  
Storage period: 1 minute

## View, modify or delete data

You have the right to view, correct or delete your personal data. You can do this yourself through the personal settings of your account. Please note that changing your email address after registration requires you to (re)confirm your new e-mail address. You also have the option to terminate your account and deleted all related information from our servers. You can find this option under ‘My account’ -> ‘Terminate account’.

If you have other questions / requests / comments about data processing, please send a specified request to support [at] heartharena.com. In order to ensure that the request for access has been made by you will have to use the same address as your account on HearthArena. We will respond to your request as soon as possible, but in any case within four weeks.

## How we protect personal data

HearthArena takes the protection of your data seriously and takes appropriate measures to prevent misuse, loss, unauthorized access, unwanted disclosure and unauthorized modification. If you feel that your data is not properly secured or there are indications of abuse, please contact our us on support [at] heartharena.com

Copyright HearthArena © 2017 

Hearthstone assets used on this site are copyrighted and/or trademarked material of Blizzard Entertainment, Inc.  
This site is not affiliated with Blizzard Entertainment, Inc.
